

Khoi Nguyen Le Minh

SENIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER REACTJS

- 10 YEARS OF EXPERIENCE
- **** +84938925905
- x nguyenkhoi2412@gmail.com
- → 391TK 42/45 Tran Hung Dao, Cau Kho Ward, District 1, Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

SUMMARY

I graduated from University of Technology and study in higher diploma in software engineering. I have over 10 years experience in web application development, especially in frontend web development. I develop HTML / CSS / and javascript coding, making the site responsive and friendlier to smaller devices is one of my main aims as well as improving performance. Through the professional knowledge I have and with my experience, I will try to do the best job at the company. Constantly strive for yourself and become the core employee of the company in the coming time.

BASIC INFORMATION

Birthday	06/01/1983
Nationality	Vietnamese
Marital Status	Married
Gender	Male

LANGUAGES



SKILLS

Front End, jQuery, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS,

Css Responsive Design, HTML5, MVC, ASP.NET,

ReactJS, Ant Design, MongoDB, SQL

EDUCATION

APTECH SCROOL

09/2001 - 08/2004

Expert programming

Higher diploma in software engineering

UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY

09/2001 - 08/2004

Information Technology

WORK HISTORY

.NET DEVELOPER

01/2022 - Current

Stepmedia Software Viet Nam (1 year 5 months)

- Development website application using MVC, SQL Server on basic platform .NET CORE, C#, MSSQL, Azure
- Frontend is using REACTJS, SASS...
- Company product development Deloitte, maintain and develop new features according to customer, reports, improve performance for APIs, troubleshooting to perfect products...
- Test and write unit tests.
- Tracing error in application insights.

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

01/2018 - 09/2020

CONEXUS VIET NAM (2 years 9 months)

- Development website application using MVC, SQL Server on basic platform .NET 4.0, 4.5...
- My specialize is develop UI with script, jquery, css responsive...
- Programming vip24, competence project. A candidate must pass a test presentation, after that, other counselor will evaluation depend on your test, and they will give some idea to help you find out an opportunity develop.
- moe project is a learning experience which aims to provide students with the opportunity to synthesise knowledge from various areas of learning, and critically and creatively apply it to real life situations. This process, which enhances students' knowledge and enables them

to acquire skills like collaboration, communication and independent learning, prepares them for lifelong learning and the challenges ahead.

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

11/2012 - 01/2018

Orient Software Development Corp. (5 years 3 months)

- Development website application using MVC, SQL Server on basic platform .NET 4.0, 4.5... And my specialize is develop UI with script, jquery, css...
- Programming vip24, competence project. A candidate must pass a test presentation, after that, other counselor will evaluation depend on your test, and they will give some idea to help you find out an opportunity develop.
- moe project. Planner create course & learner join courses to study...

DEVELOPER

06/2011 - 11/2012

VIEN NAM SOFTWARE (1 year 6 months)

- Programing projects websites for clients.
- Analysis, programming and development website application on the basic platform .NET 2.0, 3.5, 4.0... using ASP.NET, MVC, Entity Framework, Web services, html, jquery, css...

TECHNICAL SUPPORT

01/2008 - 01/2010

FPT TELECOM (2 years 1 month)

- Support clients about ADSL, LAN, WAN. Check client's connection on system, check information and all services assigned to clients.
- Support all problems that IT need to solve about Web server, mail server, FTP, IP static, NAT and troubleshoot IT's problems.
- Configure router.

CERTIFICATIONS

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

2004

University Of Technology

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

2004

FPT Aptech